Finding Aid for American Society for Information Science and Technology Records, 1925-2001
University of Michigan Library (Special Collections Research Center)
- COMMITTEES
  - Individual Committees
    - Liaison Committee
      - Individual Liaisons
        - Association for Computing Machinery (ACM)
          - Special Interest Group on Information Retrieval, 1967-1973 (Box 82)
          - Special Interest Committee on Language Analysis and Studies in the Humanities (SICLASH), 1968-1971 (Box 82)
          - General, ca. 1988 (Box 82)
        - Association for Educational Communications and Technology (AECT), 1973-1975 (Box 82)
        - Association for Health Records (AHR), 1970-1973 (Box 82)
        - Association for Library and Information Science Education (ALISE), 1983-1988 (Box 82)
        - Association for Systems Management (ASM), 1972-1973 (Box 82)
        - Association Internationale des Documentalistes (AID), 1967 (Box 82)
        - Association of American Library Schools (AALS), 1973-1974 (Box 82)
        - Association of College and Research Libraries (ACRL), 1989 (Box 82)
        - Association of Data Processing Service Organizations (ADAPSO), 1982 (Box 82)
        - Association of Earth Science Editors (AESE), 1972-1976 (Box 82)
        - Association of Population/Family Planning Libraries and Information Centers, 1974 (Box 82)
        - Association of Research Libraries (ARL), 1971-1973 (Box 82)
        - Association of Scientific Information Dissemination Centers (ASIDIC), 1971-1974 (Box 82)
        - Canadian Association for Information Science (CAIS), 1974-1975 (Box 82)
        - Committee for the Future, 1976 (Box 82)
        - Committee on National Library Information Systems (CONLIS), 1966-1968 (Box 82)
        - Computers and the Humanities Advisory Council, 1969-1974 (Box 82)
        - Conference on Population and Housing Census Users (CPHCU), 1966-1967 (Box 82)
        - Council of Biology Editors (CBE), 1969-1974 (Box 82)
        - Council of Communication Societies, 1965-1971, 2 folders (Box 82)
        - Council of National Library Associations (CNLA)
          - Correspondence, 1965-1970, 2 folders (Box 82)
          - Minutes and Agenda, 1968-1969 (Box 82)
        - Documentation Abstracts, Inc., 1972 (Box 82)
          (later name Information Science Abstracts, see also)
        - Drug Information Association (DIA), 1966-1973 (Box 82)
        - Educom, 1966-1967 (Box 82)
        - Egyptian Society for Information Technology, 1980-1982 (Box 82)
        - European Association of Scientific Information Dissemination Centers (EUSIDIC), 1971-1972 (Box 82)
        - Fall Joint Computer Conference, 1965-1969 (Box 82)
        - Federal Government Micrographics Council (FGMC), 1976 (Box 83)
        - Federal Library Committee
          - Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 83)
          - Minutes and Reports, 1971-1972 (Box 83)
        - Geoscience Information Society (GIS), 1971-1974 (Box 83)
        - Health Science Communications Association (HeSCA), 1972-1974 (Box 83)
        - Information Industry Association (IIA), 1972-1973 (Box 83)
        - Information Science Abstracts (ISA), 1971-1974 (Box 83)
          (earlier name Documentation Abstracts, see also)
        - Institute of Information Science (IIS), 1980-1981 (Box 83)
        - Institute of Management Sciences (TIMS), 1972-1974 (Box 83)
        - International Association of Documentalists and Information Officers (AID), 1967 (Box 83)
        - International Communications Association (ICA), 1972-1974 (Box 83)
        - International Federation for Documentation (FID)
          - Catalogue, 1968-1969 (Box 83)
          - Correspondence, 1965-1973 (Box 83)
          - Reports, 1967-1968 (Box 83)
          - Yearbooks, 1967-1970 (Box 83)
        - International Federation for Information Processing (IFIP), 1968 (Box 83)
        - Israel Society of Special Libraries and Information Centers, 1968 (Box 83)
        - Japan Association of Agricultural Librarians and Documentalists, 1967 (Box 83)
        - Japan Documentation Society, 1969 (Box 83)
        - Joint Council on Educational Telecommunications (JCET), 1969-1971 (Box 83)
        - Librarians' Automation Group (New South Wales), 1968 (Box 83)
        - Library Automated Systems Information Exchange, 1970 (Box 83)
        - Library Automation Research and Consulting (LARC), 1971-1973 (Box 83)
        - Library of Congress Task Force on Automation, 1968-1971 (Box 83)
        - Medical Library Association (MLA), 1967-1975 (Box 83)
        - Miscellanea, 1971-1972 (Box 83)
        - Modern Language Association, 1966-1967 (Box 83)
        - Music Library Association, 1966-1973 (Box 83)
        - National Book Committee, Inc., 1969-1970 (Box 83)
        - National Computer Conference, 1975 (Box 83)
        - National Engineering Information Conference, 1969 (Box 83)
        - National Federation of Science Abstracting and Indexing Services (NFSAIS), 1967-1971 (Box 83)
        - National Microfilm Association (NMA), 1963-1974 (Box 83)
        - National Translations Center, 1968-1973 (Box 83)
        - Office of Critical Tables, 1966-1970 (Box 83)
        - Society for Information Display, 1967-1973 (Box 83)
        - Society for Technical Communication (STC), 1964-1976 (Box 83)
        - Society of American Archivists (SAA), 1973 (Box 83)
        - Society of Technical Writers and Publishers (STWP), 1966-1971 (Box 83)
        - Special Libraries Association
          - Correspondence, 1965-1973, 3 folders (Box 83)
          - Meetings
            - Montreal and Detroit, 1969-1970 (Box 83)
            - Toronto, 1973-1974 (Box 83)
            - Chicago, 1974-1975 (Box 83)
            - Denver, 1975-1976 (Box 83)
            - New York, 1977 (Box 83)
            - Kansas City, 1977 (Box 83)
            - Detroit, 1982 (Box 83)
        - Speech Association of America, 1967-1969 (Box 83)
        - Task Force on Automation and Cooperation (TFAC), 1968-1972 (Box 83)
        - UNESCO-ICSU Central Committee to Study the Feasibility of a World Science Information System (UNISIST), 1970 (Box 83)
        - United States Book Exchange, 1964-1977 (Box 83)
        - United States National Committee International Federation for Documentation (USNCFID)
          - Correspondence, 1964-1974, 5 folders (Box 84)
          - Members, 1966-1969 (Box 84)
          - Minutes and Reports, 1964-1973 (Box 84)
          - Programs, 1966-1973 (Box 84)
        - Universal Circulation System (UNICIRC)
          - Correspondence, 1971-1975 (Box 84)
          - Exhibition Materials, 1972 (Box 84)
          - Press Releases, 1972 (Box 84)
          - Telephone Call Record, 1971-1972 (Box 84)
        - Urban Regional Information Systems Association (URISA), 1971 (Box 84)
        - World Simulation Organization, 1972-1975 (Box 84)
    - Long Range Planning, Commission on
      - Charge and Organization, 1968 and 1974 (Box 84)
      - Correspondence, 1967-1976 and 1989, 11 folders (Box 84)
      - Members, 1974 (Box 84)
      - Minutes, 1974-1975 (Box 84)
      - Mission and Goals, 1973-1975 and undated (Box 84)
      - Press Releases and Tear Sheets, 1974-1975 and 1989 (Box 84)
      - Reports, 1971-1975 and 1988-1989, 2 folders (Box 84)
    - Marketing Committee
      - Charge, 1981-1984 (Box 84)
      - Correspondence, 1979-1984 and undated (Box 84)
      - Membership, 1983-1984 (Box 84)
      - Placement Services Questionnaire Results, undated (Box 84)
      - Plan and Budget, 1980 1982 and 1986 (Box 84)
      - Reports, 1979-1987 (Box 84)
      - Survey Reports
        - Preliminary, undated (Box 84)
        - 1979-1980 (Box 84)
      - Telephone Conversation Record, 1980 (Box 84)
      - Miscellanea, 1979-1984 (Box 84)
    - Membership Committee
      - Agenda, 1981-1984 (Box 85)
      - Annual Reports, 1975-1983 (Box 85)
      - Career Brochures
        - Correspondence, 1964-1983, 2 folders (Box 85)
        - Examples, 1977-1979 (Box 85)
      - Charge, 1981 (Box 85)
      - Correspondence, 1961-1962 1964-1986 and undated, 15 folders (Box 85)
      - Focus Group, 1989 (Box 85)
      - Manual, 1979 (Box 85)
      - Membership Reports, 1969-1979 1981-1992 and 1995, 6 folders (Box 85)
        (reports on ASIS membership statistics
      - Membership Services, 1974-1981 (Box 85)
      - Minutes, 1968-1984, 3 folders (Box 85)
      - Motions, 1981 and undated (Box 85)
      - Papers Regarding Membership, 1971-1981 (Box 85)
      - Plans, 1975-1980 (Box 85)
      - Reports, 1966-1981 1984 1986-1988 1991-1992 and 1994, 6 folders (Box 86)
        (general reports on committee activities)
      - Roster, 1970-1983 (Box 86)
      - Student Membership, 1965-1968 (Box 86)
      - Surveys and Questionnaires, 1980-1981 and undated (Box 86)
      - Tear Sheets and Press Releases, 1974-1981 (Box 86)
      - Telephone Conversation Record, 1974 (Box 86)
      - Miscellanea, 1994 and undated (Box 86)
    - National Convention Committee, 1969 (Box 86)
    - Networking Committee
      (disbanded in 1986 per original folder label)
      - Action Plan, 1980 (Box 86)
      - Charge, 1981-1982 (Box 86)
      - Correspondence, 1971-1985, 3 folders (Box 86)
      - Membership, 1979-1984 (Box 86)
      - Minutes, 1975-1980 (Box 86)
      - Miscellanea, 1972-1984 (Box 86)
      - "Network Planning Paper," 1978 (Box 86)
      - Papers, 1966 and 1979-1981 (Box 86)
      - Press Releases and Tear Sheets, 1979-1982 (Box 86)
      - Reports, 1974-1984 (Box 86)
    - Nominations Committee
      - Bylaws, undated (Box 86)
      - Candidate Biography and Position Statements, A-Z, undated, 4 folders (Box 86)
      - Candidates for ASIS Office (Successful and Unsuccessful), 1964-1975 (Box 86)
      - Charge, 1981 (Box 86)
      - Correspondence, 1965-1982, 10 folders (Box 86)
      - Handbook, 1979 (Box 86)
      - Reports, 1964-1984 (Box 86)
      - Tellers Committee
        - Correspondence, 1961 (Box 86)
        - Reports, 1965-1976 (Box 86)
      - Miscellanea, 1968-1981 (Box 86)
    - Operations Planning Task Force (OPTF)
      - Correspondence, 1976-1980 (Box 87)
      - Motions, 1978 (Box 87)
      - Report
        - Drafts, April -June 1978, 3 folders (Box 87)
        - Final, October 1978 (Box 87)
      - Survey of ASIS Membership Activities, 1978, 3 folders (Box 87)
      - Survey to Evaluate Products, Services and Activities, 1977-1978, 4 folders (Box 87)
      - Survey to Evaluate Units and Their Functions, 1977, 4 folders (Box 87)
    - Organization of Information, Committee on (COI)
      - Miscellanea, 1961-1964 (Box 87)
      - Reports, 1961-1965 (Box 87)
    - Organizational Structure, Task Force on
      - Committee Charges, 1979 (Box 87)
      - Committee Reports, 1979 (Box 87)
      - Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 87)
      - Miscellanea, 1979 and undated (Box 87)
      - Report on Committees' Roles and Functions, undated (Box 87)
    - Placement Service Committee
      - Annual Reports and Minutes, 1981 and undated (Box 87)
      - Bibliography and Lecture, undated (Box 87)
      - Brochures, undated, 1976 and 1981 (Box 87)
      - Correspondence, 1962-1981 1983-1984, 10 folders (Box 87)
      - Forms, 1968 (Box 88)
      - Instructions, 1966-1976 (Box 88)
      - Job Listings, 1976 (Box 88)
      - Manual: Placement Service Reference Manual, 1979 (Box 88)
      - Members, 1967 (Box 88)
      - Notes, 1973 and undated (Box 88)
      - Plans for Placement Service, 1973 and undated (Box 88)
      - Questionnaires, 1978 ca. 1979 and undated, 2 folders (Box 88)
      - Registration, 1965-1967 (Box 88)
      - Resumes, 1968 1971-1972, 3 folders (Box 88)
      - Statistics, 1962-1973 (Box 88)
      - Miscellanea, 1970-1981 (Box 88)
    - Planning Committee
      (see also Long-Range Planning Committee)
      - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 88)
      - Notes, 1989 (Box 88)
      - Questionnaire, 1988 (Box 88)
      - Reference Materials, 1981-1986 (Box 88)
      - General, 1990 (Box 88)
    - Products and Services Task Force, 1978-1980 (Box 88)
    - Professional Enhancement Committee
      - Brochure, 1973-1975 (Box 88)
      - Charge, 1981 (Box 88)
      - Correspondence, 1970-1977, 2 folders (Box 88)
      - Membership, 1972-1976 (Box 88)
      - Miscellanea, 1970 (Box 88)
      - Papers, 1974-1976 (Box 88)
      - Reports, 1972-1976 (Box 88)
      - Survey, 1973
        - Miscellanea (Box 88)
        - Questionnaire
          - Academic (Box 88)
          - Information and Computer Center Managers (Box 88)
          - Information Systems and Computer Specialists (Box 88)
          - Librarians (Box 88)
          - Managers and Administrators (Box 88)
          - Students (Box 88)
          - Unemployed (Box 88)
          - Unknown (Box 88)
        - Results (Box 88)
      - Tear Sheets and Press Results, 1972-1976 (Box 88)
      - Telephone Call Record, 1972-1975 (Box 88)
    - Professional Leadership Committee
      (also or later called "Professional Leadership and Development Programs Committee" and "Professional Leadership Development Program")
      - Agreement, 1981 (Box 88)
      - Annual Meeting, 1991 (Box 88)
      - Correspondence, 1979-1982 and 1984, 2 folders (Box 88)
      - Membership, 1978 (Box 88)
      - Miscellanea, 1979-1982 (Box 88)
      - Reports and Minutes, 1979-1982 and undated (Box 88)
      - Tear Sheets, 1979-1980 (Box 88)
      - Workshop Participants, 1979-1981 (Box 88)
    - Professional Relations, Committee on, 1962, 2 folders (Box 88)
    - Professional Salaries Committee, 1971 (Box 89)
    - Professionalism Committee
      - Agreement, 1981 (Box 89)
      - Charge, 1981-1982 and 1986 (Box 89)
      - Correspondence, 1980-1986 and 1989 (Box 89)
      - Goals, 1980 (Box 89)
      - Members, 1980 (Box 89)
      - Motion, 1981 (Box 89)
      - Minutes and Reports, 1981-1987 and 1989 (Box 89)
    - Proprietary Rights/Use, Committee on
      - Charter, undated (Box 89)
      - Congressional Bills, 1968-1971 includes ASIS Resolution (Box 89)
      - Correspondence, 1966-1976 and undated, 6 folders (Box 89)
      - Members, 1968-1970 (Box 89)
      - Miscellanea, 1973 (Box 89)
      - Papers Regarding Copyright, 1968-1972 and undated, 2 folders (Box 89)
      - Proposal, 1969 (Box 89)
      - Reports and Minutes, 1968-1972 (Box 89)
      - Tear Sheets and Press Releases, 1970-1975 (Box 89)
      - Williams and Wilkins vs. National Library of Medicine, 1970-1972 (Box 89)
    - Public Affairs Committee
      - Charge, 1981 and 1986 (Box 89)
      - Contacts, 1989-1990 (Box 89)
      - Correspondence
        - 1966-1970 1974-1985, 9 folders (Box 89)
        - 1986-1989 and undated, 3 folders (Box 90)
      - Issue Briefs and Bills
        - General, 1979-1986, 2 folders (Box 90)
        - Informing the Nation, 1989, 2 folders (Box 90)
      - Members, 1980 and 1984-1986 (Box 90)
      - Miscellanea, 1976-1982 (Box 90)
      - Motions and Actions, 1976 and 1979-1981 (Box 90)
      - Occupational Standards, 1982 (Box 90)
      - Papers by Individuals, 1975-1984 (Box 90)
      - Papers by Organizations, 1978-1982 (Box 90)
      - Position Statements, 1987 (Box 90)
      - Press Releases, 1981-1984 (Box 90)
      - Reports and Minutes, 1968-1982 and 1984-1989, 5 folders (Box 90)
      - Tear Sheets, 1968-1985, 2 folders (Box 90)
      - Testimony before Congress
        - General, 1975-1981, 2 folders (Box 90)
        - HR 3137 1981 (Box 90)
        - HR 8395 1987 (Box 90)
      - Videotape: correspondence and other materials re PAC videotape, 1987-1988 (Box 90)
    - Public Relations Committee, 1962-1963 and 1986-1987, 2 folders (Box 90)
    - Publications Committee
      (see also Publications series)
      - ASIS Publications Catalog, undated (Box 91)
      - Action Plan, 1982-1983 (Box 91)
      - Agenda, 1969-1986, 2 folders (Box 91)
      - Annual Reports, 1970-1984 (Box 91)
      - Articles: regarding Publications, 1969 and 1982 (Box 91)
      - Awards Criteria, 1972-1982 (Box 91)
      - Bylaws, ca. 1985 (Box 91)
      - Charge, 1980-1982 (Box 91)
      - Contracts, 1986-1987 and undated (Box 91)
      - Copyright Policy, 1979 (Box 91)
      - Correspondence, 1964-1991, 25 folders (Box 91)
        (includes attachments such as agenda, minutes, and reports, especially 1990 and after)
      - Editor Review, 1979 and 1983 (Box 91)
      - Editorial Guide, undated (Box 91)
      - Editors' Reports, 1964-1982 (Box 91)
      - Exchange Agreements, 1962-1969 (Box 92)
      - Exchange Denials or Refusals, 1966-1970 (Box 92)
      - Financial Information
        - Balance Sheet, 1972-1973 (Box 92)
        - Budgets, 1968-1984 (Box 92)
        - Financial Reports, undated, 1972 and 1980 (Box 92)
        - Statement of Income, 1972 (Box 92)
        - General, 1986 (Box 92)
      - Guidelines, undated (Box 92)
      - History of Publications Program, 1975 (Box 92)
      - Issues and Concerns, 1985 (Box 92)
      - Inventory, 1976 (Box 92)
      - Members, 1971-1984 and undated (Box 92)
      - Mid-Year Meeting, 1989 (Box 92)
      - Minutes, 1969-1988 and undated, 20 folders (Box 92)
      - Minutes: Manuscript, 1985-1986 and undated, 2 folders (Box 93)
      - Minutes: from Documentation Abstracts, 1971 and 1973 (Box 93)
      - Motions and Resolutions, 1964-1981 1987 and undated, 2 folders (Box 93)
      - Objectives, undated (Box 93)
      - Pergamon Press Agreement, 1976-1977 (Box 93)
      - Policy Statements, 1971-1982 (Box 93)
      - Press Releases and Tear Sheets, 1971-1973 1988-1989, 2 folders (Box 93)
      - Procedures Subcommittee, 1976 (Box 93)
      - Proposals
        - Correspondence Proposals, 1972-1979 (Box 93)
        - Project Proposals
          - Proposals for New Publications, 1968-1981 (Box 93)
          - ADI/ASIS Publications (Serials) Programs, 1982 (Box 93)
        - Publication Proposals
          - Forms, 1973 (Box 93)
          - Manuscripts, 1973-1980 (Box 93)
          - Summary, undated (Box 93)
        - General, 1987 (Box 93)
      - Publications Program, 1971-1973 (Box 93)
      - Resolution, undated (Box 93)
      - Reports, 1965-1973 1984-1987 and 1991, 2 folders (Box 93)
      - Reports to Board of Directors, 1974-1984, 2 folders (Box 93)
      - Responsibilities, 1986 (Box 93)
      - Sales Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 93)
      - Schedules, 1972 (Box 93)
      - SIG Related Publications
        - Correspondence, 1972-1982 (Box 93)
        - Format, 1976 (Box 93)
      - Surveys, 1989-1991 (Box 93)
      - Task Force, 1988 (Box 93)
      - Tech Memo, 1969 (Box 93)
      - Telephone Record, 1971 (Box 93)
      - Miscellanea, 1970-1973 1985 and undated (Box 93)
      - ASIS Joint Publications
        - Annual Review of Biomedical Communications, 1969-1970 (Box 93)
        - FID, 1975-1976 (Box 93)
        - Information Science Abstracts: Proposal, 1975 (Box 93)
        - Key Papers
          - Agreement, 1981 and 1984 (Box 93)
          - Correspondence, 1971-1979 (Box 93)
          - Proposals, undated, 1973-1976 and 1982 (Box 93)
          - Reports, 1975-1976 (Box 93)
          - Schedule, 1980 (Box 93)
        - Scientific Information Notes
          - Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 93)
          - Financial Information, 1968 (Box 93)
            (includes grant proposal)
      - ASIS Publications
        - ARIST
          - Correspondence, 1965-1981 and undated (Box 93)
          - Proposals, 1969-1975 (Box 93)
          - Reports, 1971-1975 (Box 93)
        - BASIS
          - Proposals, 1973 and undated (Box 93)
          - Reports, 1975-1978 and 1983 (Box 93)
          - Schedule, undated (Box 93)
        - JASIS
          - Correspondence, 1971-1982 and 1990, 2 folders (Box 93)
          - Proposals, 1973 and 1979 (Box 93)
        - Proceedings, 1968-1974 (Box 93)
    - Research Committee
      - Charge, 1980-1981 (Box 94)
      - Correspondence, 1964 1981-1989 and 1994, 4 folders (Box 94)
      - Members, 1981-1984 (Box 94)
      - Motion, 1984-1986 (Box 94)
      - Reports, 1965-1987, 2 folders (Box 94)
      - Miscellanea, 1955 and 1980-1981 (Box 94)
    - Research and Technical Development, Committee on, 1962 (Box 94)
    - Science, Committee on, 1980-1981 (Box 94)
    - Science Industry Committee, 1972 (Box 94)
    - Special Membership Committee, 1961-1962 (Box 94)
    - Sponsored Projects Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 94)
    - Standards Committee
      - ANSI Subcommittee J, 1978-1979 (Box 94)
        (originally part of "Office Binder")
      - Ballot Proposals, 1971-1982, 2 folders (Box 94)
      - Ballots: Z39, 1986-1987, 6 folders (Box 94)
      - Charge, 1979-1981 (Box 94)
      - Correspondence
        (includes ballots and other attachments)
        - General
          - 1968-1979, 6 folders (Box 94)
          - 1980-1987, 13 folders (Box 95)
        - Office Binder
          - General, 1978-1979 (Box 95)
          - To and from Standards Committee, 1979-1981 (Box 95)
          - Re Standards Committee, 1979-1981 (Box 95)
      - Members
        - Main listings, 1974-1984 (Box 95)
        - Office Binder, 1979-1981 (Box 95)
      - Minutes
        - Main minutes, 1971 1980 and 1987, 2 folders (Box 95)
        - Office Binder minutes, 1978-1981, 2 folders (Box 95)
      - Miscellaneous Office Binder materials, 1978-1979 (Box 95)
      - Motions, 1973 (Box 95)
      - Press Releases, 1972-1979 (Box 95)
      - Reference, 1981-1984 (Box 95)
      - Reports
        - Annual, 1975-1984 (Box 95)
        - Quarterly, 1982-1984 (Box 95)
        - Office Binder, 1978-1981, 2 folders (Box 95)
        - Miscellaneous, 1973-1984 (Box 95)
      - Standards
        - General, 1966-1972 and undated (Box 95)
        - Office Binder
          - Standards voted on, 1978-1979 (Box 95)
          - PH5, 1979-1981 (Box 95)
          - X3, 1978-1981 (Box 95)
          - Z39
            - Bylaws, 1978-1979 (Box 95)
            - Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 95)
            - Fundraising, 1978-1979 (Box 95)
            - Voice of Z39, 1978-1979 (Box 95)
          - Z39, PH5, X3
            - Meetings, 1978-1979 (Box 95)
            - Votes and Comments, 1978-1979 (Box 95)
        - Z39
          - Ballots and related, 1981-1988, 26 folders (Box 96)
            (originally in three bound volumes; includes a small number of comments on other standards)
          - Reports, 1986, 2 folders (Box 96)
            (includes ballots)
      - Tear Sheets, 1971-1979 (Box 96)
    - State of the Art Publications, Committee on, 1962 (Box 96)
    - Statistics and Information Committee, 1965 (Box 96)
    - Student Membership Committee, 1966 (Box 96)
- AWARDS
  The AWARDS series (16 linear feet) contains materials about awards given by ASIS. These awards include the following:
  ASIS AWARDS
  The Award of Merit
  Best Chapter/SIG Publication
  Dissertation Scholarship
  Distinguished Lecturer Award
  Distinguished Service Award
  Information Science Book Award
  Kaskela Award
  JASIS Paper Award
  Non-Print Media Award
  Outstanding Information Science Teacher Award
  Student Paper Contest
  Watson Davis Award
  This series is arranged into two groups: first general awards-related materials, and then individual awards, arranged alphabetically by award name. The researcher will find a small amount of material on the Student Paper Contest in the Committees series under the Education Committee, which sponsored the contest. Materials regarding Chapters of the Year are found in the Chapters series.
  - General
    - Annual Activities Report, undated (Box 97)
    - Certificates of Appreciation, 1974-1978 (Box 97)
    - Certificates of Recognition, 1990-1994 (Box 97)
    - Correspondence, 1969-1999, 16 folders (Box 97)
    - Financial Information, 1976-1980 (Box 97)
    - Guidelines, 1979 (Box 97)
    - Jury, 1995 (Box 97)
    - Minutes, 1981 (Box 97)
    - Miscellanea, 1970-1986 (Box 97)
    - Photographs of Award Ceremonies, 1971-1983 (Box 97)
    - Press Releases, 1977-1981 (Box 97)
    - Reports, 1974-1981 (Box 97)